Luke Malinowski

Fullstack Web Developer

Address Deer Park, NY, 84043

Phone (631) 741-7803

E-mail malinowski.luke123@gmail.com

WWW https://github.com/malinowskil123

LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/luke-

malinowski-50328

Innovative fullstack web developer with knowledge in mobile responsive web development as well as strong skill and ability in writing clean and efficient code. Experience with working and integrating many third party API's. Motivated to grow and learn new technologies.



Skills

Languages: JAVA / JAVASCRIPT / NODE / SQL / HTML / CSS / SCSS

Frameworks: REACT / REDUX / EXPRESS / JQUERY / BOOTSTRAP / D3

Additional Technologies: GIT / GOOGLE CLOUD API / AMAZON AWS S3

Experience

Jan 2020 - Apr 2020 Student Full Stack Web Developer

DevMountain, Lehi, Utah

- Developed fullstack web applications using following technologies
 Javascript, Node, Postgres, React, Redux, D3, SCSS, and Amazon
 AWS
- Connected and pulled data from following external API's Google Geocode and Google Maps and Amazon S3

Aug 2018 - Current

Front End Developer

R&J Components, Hauppauge, NY

- Developed and maintained front-end code using Javascript, C# MVC, and Razor HTML
- Created more than 20+ web applications and landing pages
- Built landing pages, and responsive web applications using jQuery, and Bootstrap
- Conducted unit testing to deliver optimal browser functionality

Jeep Things

Personal Project

- Built a fullstack web application to serve as a trading platform to connect jeep owners looking to sell, buy or trade parts.
- Https://github.com/malinowskil123/jeepthings
- Http://www.jeepthingsapp.com/

Resistor Color Code Calculator

Federal Connectors

- Allows the user to input corresponding resistor color codes and then outputs a resistance value, tolerance, and failure rate.
- Written using Javascript, ¡Query and Bootstrap
- Https://federalconnectors.com/resistor-color-calc
- Https://github.com/malinowskil123/tedss-fedcon

Desktop Note Pad App

Personal Project

- Simple note pad app that allows user to save, open, and create .txt files on their desktop
- It features a status bar which tracks word count, sentence count and calculates a Flesch-Kincaid readability score (text complexity metric)
- Developed in Java using java swing GUI library
- Https://github.com/malinowskil123/java-swing-notepad

Aug 2016 - Jun 2017 Audio Engineer

Cheer Sounds, East Setauket, NY, United States

- Produced cheerleading mixes to match choreography
- Remixed instrumental tracks of pop songs to fit different time signatures
- Produced over 750+ cheerleading mixes

Education

Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

Certification: Full Stack Web Development

Dev Mountain - Lehi, UT

Won Best Technology Award For Personal Project

Aug 2018 - Dec 2019 Associate of Science: Computer Science

Suffolk Community College - Selden, NY

- In progress
- Completed 40 credits towards an Associate's Degree in Computer Science
- Relevant Courses: (JAVA) Fundamentals Of Computer Science,
 Object Oriented Programming, Data Structures and Algorithms

Sep 2012 - May 2016 E

Bachelor of Professional Studies: Business Mgmt. / Audio Tech

Five Towns College - Dix Hills, NY

Graduated with 3.0 GPA